Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Staff Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Gillum, Linda, 1991-2005; 4.6 linear feet
  - Committees
    - Provost's Council on Student Honors
      - Scholarship Representatives, 2001-2002 (Box 427)
      - Scholarship Representatives Advisory Group, 2001-2002 (Box 427)
      - Scholarship Societies, 1999-2000 (Box 427)
      - Shipman Scholars
        - Miscellaneous, 2001-2003 (Box 427)
        - Receptions, 2001-2003 (Box 427)
        - Shipman Society Meeting Minutes, 2001-2003 (Box 427)
        - Weekend, 2001-2003 (Box 427)
      - Website and Guidebook, 2001-2002 (Box 427)
    - Public Goods Council
      - General, 2002-2004 (Box 427)
      - Article, 2003 (Box 427)
      - Arts of Citizenship, 2004 (Box 427)
      - Brochure, 2004 (Box 427)
      - Curricular Models Task Force, 2002-2003 (Box 427)
      - Fellowship Applications
        - 2002 (Box 427)
        - 2003 (Box 428)
        - 2004 (Box 428)
      - Fellowship Program, 2002-2004 (Box 428)
      - Logos, 2002 (Box 428)
      - Meeting Information, 2001-2002 (Box 428)
      - Meetings
        - 1999 (Box 428)
        - 2000 (Box 428)
        - 2001 (Box 428)
        - 2002 (Box 428)
        - January 9, 2003 (Box 428)
        - February 6, 2003 (Box 428)
        - March 6, 2003 (Box 428)
        - April 3, 2003 (Box 428)
        - May 1, 2003 (Box 428)
        - June 5, 2003 (Box 428)
        - September 4, 2003 (Box 428)
        - October 2, 2003 (Box 428)
        - January 8, 2004 (Box 428)
        - February 5, 2004 (Box 428)
        - March 4, 2004 (Box 428)
        - April 1, 2004 (Box 428)
        - May 6, 2004 (Box 428)
        - June 3, 2004 (Box 428)
        - July 1, 2004 (Box 428)
        - September 9, 2004 (Box 428)
        - December 17, 2004 (Box 428)
      - Member Information, 1999-2003 (Box 428)
        (includes photographs)
      - Property Disposition, 2003 (Box 428)
      - Senior Fellowship, 2005 (Box 428)
    - Undergraduate Admissions Advisory Committee (UAAC), 1999-2000 (Box 428)
  - Conferences
    - Oxford Roundtable
      - General, 2000 (Box 428)
      - Slides, 2000 (Box 428)
  - Projects
    - South Africa Initiatives Office, 1999-2000 (Box 428)
    - Undergraduate Admissions Project, 1996-2002; 3 folders (Box 428)
    - Undergraduate Commission (UC)
      - Academic Program Group (APG), 2002 (Box 428)
      - Admissions -- Cases Involving Conduct and/or Crime, 1999-2000 (Box 428)
      - Admissions/Recruitment, 1999 (Box 428)
      - Appendices (Final Report)
        - Appendix Guide (Box 428)
        - Appendix I: History and Subcommittee Reports, 2000 (Box 428)
        - Appendix II: Overview of Undergraduate Education, 1997-2001 (Box 428)
        - Appendix III: Undergraduate Initiatives at Peer Institutions, 2000-2001 (Box 428)
        - Appendix IV: Learning Communities, 1999-2001 (Box 428)
        - Appendix V: Residential Housing, 1999-2001 (Box 428)
        - Appendix VI: Civic Responsibility, 1999-2001 (Box 428)
        - Appendix VII: Public Goods, 2001 (Box 428)
        - Appendix VIII: Diversity, 1999-2001 (Box 428)
        - Appendix IX: Surveys, Assessments, and Evaluations, 1992-2001 (Box 428)
        - Appendix X: Admissions and Enrollment, 1999-2001 (Box 429)
        - Appendix XI: New Student Orientation and Advising, 2001 (Box 429)
        - Appendix XII: Teaching and Learning, 1997-2001 (Box 429)
        - Appendix XIII: Financial Aid and Scholarships, 1999-2001 (Box 429)
        - Appendix XIV: International and Global Experiences, 1999-2001 (Box 429)
        - Supplemental Appendix 1: Undergraduate Education, 1994-2001; 2 folders (Box 429)
        - Supplemental Appendix 2: Undergraduate Admissions and Enrollment, 2001 (Box 429)
        - Supplemental Appendix 3: Undergraduate Financial Aid and Scholarship, 2001 (Box 429)
        - Supplemental Appendix 4: Undergraduate Residential Housing, 1997-2001 (Box 429)
        - Supplemental Appendix 5: Learning Communities, 2001 (Box 429)
        - Supplemental Appendix 6: International and Global Experiences, 2001 (Box 429)
      - Articles, 2000 (Box 429)
      - Arts of Citizenship, 1999-2001 (Box 429)
      - Background, 2000 (Box 429)
      - Background Materials, 1999 (Box 429)
      - Background -- Peer Institutions, 2000-2001 (Box 429)
      - Budget Information, 1996-1998 (Box 429)
      - Campus Neighborhoods, undated (Box 429)
      - Cantor, Nancy -- Remarks, 1999-2000 (Box 429)
      - Center for Human Growth and Development -- Minority International Research Training (MIRT), 2000-2001 (Box 429)
      - Committee Reports -- "A Michigan Education, 1991 (Box 429)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 429)
      - Couzens Hall -- Shared Space, 2000 (Box 429)
      - Data, 1999 (Box 429)
      - Department of Linguistics, 1999 (Box 429)
      - Final Report, 2001 (Box 429)
      - Financial Aid, undated (Box 429)
      - First Year Experience
        - Background, 1996 (Box 429)
        - Restructuring First Year Experience, 1995-1996 (Box 429)
      - General Files, 2000-2001 (Box 429)
      - Honors, undated (Box 429)
      - International Student Organizations, 2000 (Box 429)
      - International Studies, 1999 (Box 429)
      - Internships, 2000 (Box 429)
      - Jerome Weisner Symposium, 1999 (Box 429)
      - July Interim Reports, 2000 (Box 429)
      - Language Resource Center, 2000 (Box 429)
      - Life Sciences and Undergraduate Experience, 1999 (Box 429)
      - Meetings
        - February 21, 2000 (Box 429)
        - March 7, 2000 (Box 429)
        - March 30, 2000 (Box 429)
        - April 6, 2000 (Box 429)
        - April 25, 2000 (Box 430)
        - May 16, 2000 (Box 430)
        - May 31, 2000 (Box 430)
        - June 6, 2000 (Box 430)
        - June 13, 2000 (Box 430)
        - September 5, 2000 (Box 430)
        - October 17, 2000 (Box 430)
        - November 10, 2000 (Box 430)
        - December 7, 2000 (Box 430)
        - January 31, 2001 (Box 430)
        - February 20, 2001 (Box 430)
        - May 8, 2001 (Box 430)
        - February 1, 2002 (Box 430)
      - Meetings, Minutes and Agendas, 2000-2001 (Box 430)
      - Meeting Summaries, 2000-2001 (Box 430)
      - Michigan Learning Communities (MLC)
        - Background (Box 430)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 430)
        - Meetings, 1999-2000 (Box 430)
        - Technology Report, 2000 (Box 430)
        - Transition Documents, 1999-2000 (Box 430)
      - Michigan Student Study, 1996-2002 (Box 430)
      - Miscellaneous, 1996-2000 (Box 430)
      - National Learning Communities Program, 1998-2002 (Box 430)
      - Notes, undated (Box 430)
      - Peer Institution Survey Results, 2000 (Box 430)
      - Presentation to Library Directors, 2001 (Box 430)
      - Presentations, undated (Box 430)
      - President's Advisory Group, 1999 (Box 430)
      - Proposals, 1999-2002 (Box 430)
      - Public Forums, 2000 (Box 430)
      - Public Goods, 1998-2000 (Box 430)
      - Report on the Recruitment and Scholarship Committee, undated (Box 430)
      - Residential Housing Proposals from the Sub-Committees of the Undergraduate Commission, 1998-2000 (Box 430)
      - Subcommittees
        - General Files, undated (Box 430)
        - Sub-committee I: Connecting Size and Scale, 2000 (Box 430)
        - Sub-committee II: Connecting Globally, 2000 (Box 430)
          - International and Global Undergraduate Experience preliminary report, August 21, 2000
        - Sub-committee II: Inkelas Material, 2000; 3 folders (Box 430)
        - Sub-committee III: Connecting Campus Committees, 2000 (Box 430)
      - Summary of Issues, 2001 (Box 430)
      - Summary of Meetings, 2000 (Box 430)
      - Talking Points, 2001 (Box 430)
      - "The Freshman Year Experience", 1999 (Box 430)
      - Undergraduate Council
        - Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 430)
        - Meetings
          - April --, May; 2002 (Box 430)
          - January 2003 (Box 430)
          - February 2003 (Box 431)
          - April 2003 (Box 431)
          - Deans Meeting, Fall, 2003 (Box 431)
          - September 8, 2003 (Box 431)
          - October 1, 2003 (Box 431)
          - November 5, 2003 (Box 431)
          - December 3, 2003 (Box 431)
          - January 14, 2004 (Box 431)
          - February 4, 2004 (Box 431)
          - June 16, 2004 (Box 431)
        - Membership, 2003 (Box 431)
        - Subcommittee, 2003 (Box 431)
        - Subcommittee Leads Meeting, 2002 (Box 431)
      - Undergraduate Library, 2001 (Box 431)
      - Website, 2000-2001 (Box 431)
      - Working Group on Faculty, undated (Box 431)
      - Working Group on Undergraduate Education, undated (Box 431)
    - Undergraduate Research Council, 2000 (Box 431)
- Weiss, Janet, 1998-2004; 0.6 linear feet
  Janet Weiss joined the Provost's office in 2002 when she was appointed Associate Provost for Academic Affairs, a position that evolved to be responsible for academic affairs, faculty affairs, and academic human resources. She served in this capacity until 2005, when she was appointed Vice Provost for Academic Affairs -- Graduate Studies and Dean of the Rackham Graduate School, responsible for administering graduate programs of the University. Her records form one series, Topical Files (0.6 lin. ft.), dating from her before becoming Dean, and include documentation on several child care initiatives at the University, the merger of the Matthaei Botanical Gardens and Nichols Arboretum, and other subjects. Records pertaining to Weiss's service as Dean of the Rackham Graduate School may be found in the Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies (University of Michigan) records.
  - Topical Files
    - Capital Projects
      - General, 2002-2004 (Box 431)
      - Debt, 2002 (Box 431)
    - Child Care Access Means Parents in School Program (CCAMPIS)
      - Grant, 2001 (Box 431)
      - Incentives, 2002 (Box 431)
    - Child Care Report, 2002 (Box 431)
    - Child Care Task Force Report, 1998 (Box 431)
    - Child Care Tuition Grant, 2003-2004 (Box 431)
    - Committee on Student Parent Issues (COSPI)
      - General, 2002-2004; 4 folders (Box 431)
      - Data Collection, 2002 (Box 431)
      - GEO Settlement, 2002 (Box 431)
      - Task Force Report, 2001 (Box 431)
    - Conflict of Interest/Conflict of Commitment (CIC/COC), 2002-2005 (Box 431)
    - Kids Kare at Home Annual Reports, 2001-2004
      - Background, 2003-2004 (Box 431)
      - Committee Report, 2003 (Box 431)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 431)
      - Job Descriptions, undated (Box 431)
      - Merger Meetings, 2002-2004 (Box 431)
      - Merger Models, 2002-2003 (Box 431)
      - Parking, 2002 (Box 431)
    - Provost's Academic Leadership Task Force, 2004 (Box 431)
- Van der Pluijm, Ben, 1998-2004; 0.5 linear feet
  Ben van der Pluijm, Professor of Geology and Professor of Environment, joined the University faculty in 1985. In 2007, Provost Teresa Sullivan appointed him as senior counselor to the Provost for University accreditation. His records (0.5 lin. ft.) document his activities relating to the 2010 accreditation process and have been included in the Provost's Staff Files.
  - Accreditation
    - AAU Survey, 2008 (Box 432)
    - Accreditation Working Group Reports, 2009 (Box 432)
    - Alumni Survey, 2009 (Box 432)
    - Annual Advising Summit, 2007 (Box 432)
    - Chair and Associate Dean Leadership Program, 2007-2008 (Box 432)
    - College Learning Assessment -- Pilot, 2008 (Box 432)
    - Forum on Internationalization, 2009 (Box 432)
    - General Information, 2007 (Box 432)
    - Ginsberg Center, 2007-2008 (Box 432)
    - Global Engagement, 2009-2010 (Box 432)
    - Higher Learning Commission, 2009 (Box 432)
    - Higher Learning Commission Annual Reports, 2001-2007 (Box 432)
    - Information Meetings, 2007 (Box 432)
    - National Survey of Student Engagement, 2006-2008 (Box 432)
    - Notes on Unit Accreditation Reports, 2009 (Box 432)
    - Provost's Forum -- Campus Learning Environment, 2009 (Box 432)
    - Rackham PhD Survey, 2009 (Box 432)
    - Report
      - Acquisition, Discovery, and Application of Knowledge, 2009 (Box 432)
      - Engagement and Service, 2009 (Box 432)
      - Learning Environment, 2009 (Box 432)
      - Mission and Integrity, 2009 (Box 432)
      - Preparing for the Future, 2009 (Box 432)
    - Resource Room, 2010 (Box 432)
    - UM Flint Accreditation, 2007 (Box 432)
    - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP), 2007 (Box 432)
    - Unit Assessments of the Student Learning Environment, 2008 (Box 432)
    - Voluntary System of Accountability (VSA), 2007-2008 (Box 432)
- Schmidt, Sharron, 1998-2004
  Sharron Schmidt was the Office Manager for Human Resources and Affirmative Action in the Provost's Office from 2004-2006. In this role, one of her responsibilities was coordinating meetings between the provost and various staff members. Her files are arranged in one series, Provost's Meetings, and consist of 0.65 lin. ft. of records from these one-on-one meetings between the provost and provost's staff members. In 2006, Schmidt became an Assistant to the Provost.
  - Provost Meetings
    - Butterfield, Barbara, 2003 (Box 433)
    - Coleman, Mary Sue, 2005-2006 (Box 433)
    - Gibbons, Karen, 2006 (Box 433)
    - Hanlon, Phil
      - General, 2005-2006 (Box 433)
      - Appointments, 2005-2006 (Box 548)
    - King, John, 2006 (Box 433)
    - Knepp, Marilyn
      - General, 2003-2006; 3 folders (Box 433)
      - Appointments, 2003-2005 (Box 548)
      - General Counsel, 2004 (Box 548)
        [Patient/client records restricted until July 01, 2104 ]
      - Students, 2004 (Box 548)
        [Student records restricted until July 01, 2089 ]
      - Lewis, Earl, 2003-2004 (Box 433)
    - Lichter, Allen
      - General, 2003-2005 (Box 433)
      - Appointments, 2005 (Box 548)
    - Monts, Lester
      - General, 2003-2006; 4 folders (Box 433)
      - Appointments, 2003-2005 (Box 548)
      - General Counsel, 2003-2005 (Box 548)
        [Patient/client records restricted until July 01, 2105 ]
      - Students, 2004-2005 (Box 548)
        [Student records restricted until July 01, 2090 ]
      - Pierce, Lori (Box 433)
      - General, 2006 (Box 433)
      - Appointments, 2006 (Box 548)
      - Students, 2006 (Box 548)
        [Student records restricted until July 01, 2091 ]
      - Provost Advisory Faculty Committee (PFAC), 2004-2005 (Box 433)
    - Raymond, Pamela, 2005 (Box 433)
    - Rudgers, Lisa
      - General, 2003-2005 (Box 433)
      - Appointments, 2005 (Box 548)
      - Shaw, Catherine, 2006 (Box 433)
    - Tedesco, Lisa
      - General, 2003-2005 (Box 433)
      - Appointments, 2004-2005 (Box 548)
      - Students, 2004 (Box 548)
      - Tessler, Mark (Box 433)
      - General, 2004-2006 (Box 433)
      - Appointments, 2005-2006 (Box 548)
      - Whitaker, Gil, 2005 (Box 433)
- Bauer, Kathleen/Hilton, James, 1999-2006; 0.85 linear feet
  Kathleen (Kati) Bauer and James L. Hilton's records (0.85 lin. ft.) document information technology matters on campus. James Hilton began his career at the University as a faculty member in the Psychology Department. In 2000, Provost Nancy Cantor appointed him a special assistant to the Provost to head up a task force looking into media rights, particularly in regard to digital content. In 2001, he joined the provost's office as the Associate Provost for Academic Information and Instructional Technology, serving as the Interim University Librarian for a year in 2005. He left the University in 2006 to serve as Vice President and Chief Information Officer at the University of Virginia, but returned to the University of Michigan and the Provost's Office in 2013 with appointments as professor in the School of Information, Dean of Libraries and University Librarian, and Vice Provost for Digital Educational Initiatives.
  Kati Bauer began working for the University in 1976, and moved into technology related roles in 1988. Between 1997 and 2001, she held various roles under the University's chief information officer, José-Marie Griffiths. In 2001, she became Assistant to the Associate Provost for Information Technology, the post being held at the time by James L. Hilton. Bauer held this position until 2010, when she moved to the office of Vice Provost of International Affairs. In 2013, she rejoined Hilton, working under him in his role as Dean of Libraries.
  The records of Kathleen Bauer date mainly from Hilton's work in the Provost's Office as Associate Provost for Academic Information and Bauer's service as assistant. It is not always clear which participant created the records; therefore the records have been arranged jointly under Hilton and Bauer. These records relate to matters pertaining to IT infrastructure, issues, and policy development affecting campus, including a number of files related to copyright and media rights.
  As well as records created jointly with Hilton, a series of records exists in which Bauer is the sole creator. The Kathleen Bauer records (0.4 lin. ft.) are similar in nature to the Kati Bauer and James Hilton records, documenting matters relating to campus IT, and are arranged in one Topical Files series and differ primarily in ownership.
  - Topical Files
    - Commercial Notetaking, 2000 (Box 433)
    - Computerworld Honors Program, 1999-2004 (Box 433)
    - Conflict of Interest/Conflict of Commitment (COI/CIC)
      - General, 2004-2005 (Box 433)
      - General Counsel, 2005 (Box 548)
    - Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network (CIESIN), 1997 (Box 433)
    - Copyright
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 2000-2001 (Box 433)
      - Fair Use Forum, 2001 (Box 433)
      - General Counsel, 2001 (Box 548)
      - Intellectual Property, 2001-2002 (Box 433)
      - "Intellectual Property and Academic Tradition: You Can Run but You Cannot Hide", by James Hilton and Jonathan Alger, undated (Box 433)
      - Intellectual Property Policies Committee (IPPC), 2000-2002; 2 folders (Box 433)
      - Intellectual Property Policy (IPP) Governing Bylaw Committee, 2003 (Box 434)
      - Ownership, 2000 (Box 434)
      - Queries, 2004-2005 (Box 434)
      - Recommendations, 2001-2002 (Box 434)
      - Symposium, 2001 (Box 434)
      - Talking Points, 2002 (Box 434)
      - Website Information, 2001 (Box 434)
    - Entertainment Provider Companies, 2004-2006 (Box 434)
    - Fiber, 2004-2005 (Box 434)
    - Janus Project (Box 434)
    - Liaisons on Media Rights and Intellectual Property (IP), 2000 (Box 434)
    - My.umich.edu
      - General, 2001 (Box 434)
      - Letters, 2001-2002 (Box 434)
    - Napster, 2000 (Box 434)
    - SBC Ameritech
      - Events, 2001-2002 (Box 434)
      - Grant, 2002 (Box 434)
      - Initiative, 1997-2000 (Box 434)
      - Publicity Documents, 2000-2001 (Box 434)
      - Reports, 1998-2003 (Box 434)
    - Spoof/Spam Policy, 2002-2005 (Box 434)
- Bauer, Kathleen, 1976; 2000-2009
  - Topical Files
    - Affiliation Agreements -- History, 2000-2004 (Box 503)
    - Domain Names, 2001-2009 (Box 503)
    - File Sharing, 2003-2009; 3 folders (Box 503)
      - File Sharing Clips
      - File Sharing Appendices
    - Ford Library, 1976; 2007 (Box 503)
    - Information Technology (IT) Commons -- Chavez/Cohen Consulting, 2003-2008 (Box 503)
    - VMerse/CAD Corporation, 2007-2009 (Box 503)
- Knepp, Marilyn, 1996-2006; 8.1 linear feet
  Marilyn Knepp also maintained files on her responsibilities outside of budgeting. These files (8.1 lin. ft.) have been arranged into two series: Committees and Topical Files. The Committees series contains minutes, agendas, and other materials for various committees and projects Knepp served on, including the Administrative Data Delivery Advisory Group (ADDAG), the Committee on Health Insurance Premium Design (CHIPD), the Enrollment Working Group (EWG), and the University Budget and Finance Group (UBFG). Projects include MPathways and the Classification System Project, which focused on the re-classification of job titles within the University.
  - Committees, 1996-2001
    - Administrative Data Delivery Advisory Group (ADDAG)
      - Agendas and Minutes
        - 1999-2001 (Box 421)
        - 2002 (Box 421)
        - 2003 (Box 421)
      - Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 421)
      - Group Charge (Major Tasks), 1999-2001 (Box 421)
      - Membership, 2000-2001 (Box 421)
      - Michigan Administrative Information Services (MAIS), 2001-2003 (Box 421)
      - Policy Groups and Subgroups, ca. 2000-2001 (Box 421)
      - Recommendations and Reports, 1996-2001; 2 folders (Box 421)
  - Committees, 1996-2006
    - Administrative Data Delivery Advisory Group (ADDAG)
      - Agendas and Minutes
        - 1999-2001 (Box 439)
        - 2002 (Box 439)
        - 2003 (Box 439)
      - Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 439)
      - Group Charge (Major Tasks), 1999-2001 (Box 439)
      - Membership, 2000-2001 (Box 439)
      - Michigan Administrative Information Services (MAIS), 2001-2003 (Box 439)
      - Policy Groups and Subgroups, ca. 2000-2001 (Box 439)
      - Recommendations and Reports, 1996-2001; 2 folders (Box 439)
    - Committee on Health Insurance Premium Design (CHIPD)
      - "2000 Open Enrollment Process: Customer Satisfaction Survey", 2001 (Box 439)
      - Background Book, 2003; 2 folders (Box 439)
      - Background Data, 2003 Comments, 2003 (Box 439)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 439)
      - Final Report, 2003 (Box 439)
      - General, 2003 (Box 439)
      - Meetings
        - June --, July 2002 (Box 440)
        - November 2002-January 2003 (Box 440)
        - February 2003-May 2003 (Box 440)
        - June 2003 (Box 440)
        - July 2003 (Box 440)
        - August 2003 (Box 440)
        - September 2003 (Box 440)
        - Undated (Box 440)
      - "Prescription Drug Work Group 2002", 2000 (Box 440)
      - Presentations, 2003 (Box 440)
      - Reports, 2001-2005 (Box 440)
      - "The University of Michigan Post-Retirement Benefits Study", 2002 (Box 440)
      - Working Models, 2003; 3 folders (Box 440)
    - Classification System Project
      - Career Family Classification System, 2005 (Box 440)
        - Supervisor's Toolkit
          [Executive records restricted until July 1, 2025 ]
      - Meetings
        - 2001 (Box 440)
        - 2002, 5 folders (Box 440)
        - 2003, 3 folders (Box 440)
        - 2004, 3 folders (Box 441)
        - 2005 (Box 441)
    - Enrollment Working Group (EWG)
      - 1999 (Box 441)
      - 2000, 2 folders (Box 441)
      - 2001, 2 folders (Box 441)
      - 2002, 3 folders (Box 441)
      - 2003, 2 folders (Box 441)
        - Office of Undergraduate Admissions Data Tracking, October 31, 2003
          [Executive records restricted until July 1, 2023 ]
      - 2003-2004 (Box 441)
      - 2004 (Box 441)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 441)
      - 2005, 2 folders (Box 442)
      - 2006 (Box 442)
    - MPathways
      - 1997-1998 (Box 442)
      - 1998, 2 folders (Box 442)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 442)
      - 1999-1999-2000 (Box 442)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 442)
      - Budget, 1999 (Box 442)
      - E-mail Responses, 1998 (Box 442)
      - Human Resources, 1998 (Box 442)
      - Human Resource Management System (HRMS) (Box 442)
        - General, 1998-2000; 2 folders (Box 442)
        - HR Discrepancy Report, 2002-2003 (Box 442)
        - Stabilization Meeting, 2002 (Box 442)
        - Status Meeting, 2001 (Box 442)
        - Strategic Plan, 2003-2004 (Box 442)
        - Upgrade, 2003-2004 (Box 442)
    - Miscellaneous Committees
      - Academic Program Group, 2002 (Box 442)
      - Advisory Committee on University Budgets (ACUB), 1999-2000 (Box 442)
      - Associate Provosts and Associate Deans Group (APADG), 2001-2002 (Box 442)
      - Associate Provosts and Associate Deans Group (APADG) Mentoring Steering Committee, 2000 (Box 442)
      - Budget Administrator's Group